Six Months Earlier
You're tougher than the rumors
suggested, Red Gelato!
And Today
Watch this, everyone!
I'm currently looking down on the battle
raging between the Gelato 5 and Gekko.
Look at this! The action is
too intense to turn away!
These heroes are fighting
for the peace of our world!
And now...
Red Gelato and Reaper
Princess are facing off!
It's a true battle between aces!
LIVE FROM THE SKIES ABOVE THE CITY
Go!
If you're watching this at home,
please join me in cheering for Red!
I'll feint with a left hook,
leading into a right inside low kick.
Watch for it!
I'll block the low kick and
lead into a right high kick.
You should duck!
Understood!
Impressive indeed, Red.
Let's move this elsewhere, Reaper Princess!
Look at that!
They're heading off to have a duel!
For those who missed the previous episode,
Allow me to explain!
allow me to explain once more!
Red Gelato of Freezing Sentai
Gelato 5, Fudo Aikawa,
and combatant for Secret Society Gekko,
Reaper Princess, A.K.A. Desumi Magahara,
are dating!
Episode 2    The Truth About Dating
By the way... Desumi-san.
What is it, Fudo?
We seem a bit further away
than usual, don't we?
D-Do you think?
This feels normal to me...
It's really not!
We're usually much—
Stay back! Don't come any closer!
Rejected
No, it's not like that!
I just... I was really active today, so...
I'm probably smelly.
Oh so cute...
So, I just...
I swear never to leave you, Desumi-san,
no matter how you may smell!
Don't say it that way!
Why are you so insensitive?!
I'll just spend the rest of
the day looking this way.
I've never known anyone so charming!
Wh-What are you doing?!
I love you, even when you're angry!
H-Hey!
Fine, whatever!
Stop it, you jerk!
You can't share the pictures
if you use a camera like that one.
Use my smartphone.
You have to scooch in more.
tha-thump
We-We're closer..
We-We're so much closer...
tha-thump
...than we've ever been!
The magic of the camera is a powerful thing!
And...
Just as I thought...
You smell wonderful, Desumi-san!
Hey, eyes open!
R-Right...
Hey, Red!
Not good!
We're finished up over there!
Did she see—
Hey, you beat Reaper Princess!
Death...
Great job, Fudo!
Nicely done, Desumi-san!
We'd better get back fast!
Not so fast!
The TV station requested
an interview before we go!
Interview?!
Red-san! Could I have an interview?
I'm here with some questions for Fudo Aikawa,
high school student and
ever-reliable leader of Gelato 5.
H-Hey there.
I'm Fudo Aikawa!
Red's on!
It looks like you won your
duel with Reaper Princess,
and kept the earth at peace once more!
I-Indeed.
I understand that Reaper Princess is an
extremely powerful and fearsome combatant.
How do you feel about her, Red-san?
How do I feel about her?
Let me see...
There's no one else like her!
Blush
The day I first met her,
my heart was pounding so fast,
I couldn't sleep that night!
Bluuush
I sometimes spend an entire day
thinking of nothing but her!
Did she move just now?
J-Just your imagination!
Just kill me already!
So she's an indispensable
rival to fuel your own growth,
and you approach every fight
with great caution?
You may be Mr. Stoic, Red-san, but you're
still in the prime of your youth!
So let's move to that question!
Here it comes!
Do you have a girlfriend?!
All the Red fans out there are dying to know!
Well...
I want to say I do, and that she's here!
Please! Fudo'd never have a girlfriend!
Look at these muscles!
Bodybuilding's all he
thinks about, morning 'til night!
Aw, what a waste!
A lot of his female fans find that
simplicity of his very charming!
Even ones I know personally!
Yeah, right!
But I guess it would do for you to learn
a little bit about the feminine heart.
So we're taking applications
for a date with Red!
Look for details on the screen right now!
Please stop, Misaki-neesan.
Maybe I'll try my luck!
Anyway, back to you guys in the studio!
It's safe now, Desumi-san.
hrmph
Desumi-san?
Are you angry?
Of course not.
Though you do seem to be very popular.
Fudo-kun with the rapidly
expanding female fanbase...
There's nothing for you to worry about!
You're the only girl for me!
I wonder about that.
It's true!
I would do anything for you!
You would really do anything?
Of course I would!
Then... would you take me out on a real date?
I felt so sure I'd never get a
chance to do something like this.
But I always wanted it...
To go with my sweetheart on a real... date.
Allow me to explain!
A date is an event in which
two people choose a day of the week,]
meet up, and get to know each other better!
I can easily take you on a real date!
Really?!
Yes!
We'll meet up tomorrow at
five o'clock in Central Park!
Yes!
But...
What in the world do you do on a real date?
T-Too many choices...
Planetarium
Movie
Meet up to go shopping
Things to enjoy as a couple!
Dating recs
Recommended spots
Theme Park
Dinner
Classy Spots For Cultured Adults
Aquarium
Drive
Zoo
Not good.
At this rate...
Date Plan
It will be tomorrow before
I settle on anything!
The Latest Dating Spots
Whatcha up to, Fudo?
BEER
Lookin' up more muscle stuff?
Misaki-neesan...
You smell like beer.
Popular Places for Love!
Learn About All the Trends!
The Latest Dating Spots
Well, well!
Wouldja look at that!
It's because I said that thing on
TV about takin' dating applications!
So now you're doin' homework!
Well... something like that.
But I can't figure out what
an ideal date would look like.
Look at you, all serious!
There aren't really any rules.
All that matters is you pick
out something you both enjoy!
I... I see!
Date Plan
In that instant, the seemingly insurmountable
wall in my mind began to crumble!
I had arrived at the truth about dating!
Love After World Domination!
Okay!
The civilians around me
don't seem to have noticed.
My disguise is perfect!
No one will interrupt our precious date!
It should be about time, right?
But now that it comes down to it...
I do find myself nervous.
Hey, Fudo!
Sorry, did I keep you waiting?
squee
Desumi's in plain clothes!
Something about meeting up formally like this
makes me feel a little self-conscious...
Is she capable of doing
anything that isn't precious?!
That's quite the disguise, Fudo!
Actually, other than the
glasses and the hair,
it's all my usual style.
R-Really? It suits you, Fudo.
So, what will we be doing today?
No need to worry there!
Today's Date
I've worked it all out in advance!
A date plan!
Let's begin, Desumi-san!
Right!
Here! This is where we'll start!
Fudo, what is this?
The Gotanda branch of that historic
training gym, Kin-niku Gym!
Would you look at those two!
Well done, Desumi-san!
You're really hitting it!
Go on! Blast those triceps!
Reach for those glimmering trapezius muscles!
Play through the pain to
build those adductors!
Next up, running!
Running?!
Something Desumi-san and I can both enjoy...
Training, of course!
I didn't know it could be this fun
to do things I normally do
on my own with someone else.
Dating is wonderful!
How are you feeling, Desumi-san?
Are you starting to get hungry?
Let's have a meal.
Oh, dinner?
That sounds great!
And there's something I'd really
like to discuss with you.
What could it be? I can't wait!
Here, this one's for you.
Protein Bar
Low Sugar
And there's plenty more where that came from!
Now, as for what I wanted to discuss...
Desumi-san, which insect do you think
would be strongest if it was a giant?
I think—
I need to go to the bathroom.
Yes! Nice work, Fudo!
It's all gone perfectly so far!
After this, it's the main event!
The human anatomy exhibit!
Human Anatomy Exhibit
Tokyo Hero Museum of Art
She's just going to love this!
Oh, Fudo?
Misaki-neesan? What is it?
It's about that advice
I gave you yesterday...
Just forget all that.
What?
I was pretty drunk, and I think I
told you there weren't any rules...
But I guess there kind of are.
C-Could you tell me what they are?
For... future reference.
The first one's about your appearance.
I'm betting you'll want to go
in a tight-fitting tank top,
but don't even think about it.
Make yourself presentable, okay?
And since the girl will probably
be dressing up a bit herself,
avoid any activities that might
make her sweat or get dirty.
And be sure to get reservations
at a halfway decent restaurant.
But I'll bet you didn't need
me to tell you that stuff, huh?
After that, stick to talk of sweets
or something, and you'll be fine.
"Which insect
do you
think would
be strongest
if it was
a giant?"
Which insect do you think would
be strongest if it was a giant?
Well, that's all! So long!
I got it all wrong.
This wasn't a real date at all.
It's no wonder she hasn't come back.
Please forgive me, Desumi-san!
Next time...
I promise to create a date
plan that you'll enjoy!
So, please...
Please, give me one more chance!
Desumi-san...
freeze
shiver
What are you doing, Fudo?
Desumi-san!
You came back?!
I went to buy drinks,
but the store was crowded,
so I got stuck there a while.
You know how...
these things make your mouth dry
unless you have something to drink?
I eat them sometimes myself, so I know.
Now, what were you saying
about the strongest insect?
Impossible...
What's impossible?
Are you saying... you were
actually enjoying this date?
What's with you, Fudo?
You've been acting a little
weird for a while now.
W-Well... see...
Y-You aren't angry, Desumi-san?
Of course I'm not!
But it's nice to know that you
worry about these things, too.
Well, sure...
I'm just happy knowing you made
up that whole plan for me.
I'm content just being out with you.
The world might think
it's weird, but who cares?
We are who we are.
Let's go easy on ourselves, Fudo.
This is...
Just like it was that day.
Fudo?
What is this...
this all-new feeling?!
I-It's a call!
Y-Y-Yeah, looks like it!
Well, I should be going.
Y-Yeah...
See you later!
Wretched heroes...
I'm here for payback!
Too bad you'll just get more of the same!
Let's go!
Hey, Red!
We're fighting, here!
bliss
Come on, man!
What's wrong with you, Reaper Princess?!
This is the Gekko
women's dorm
(pets allowed)
This is the Gekko women's dorm.
Many of the female staffers who work
for Secret Society Gekko live here.
My name is Hellko.
Were you a good girl while I was gone?!
hugs
I am the precious little kitty of
Reaper Princess, A.K.A. Desumi Magahara.
I'm told that there are many who tremble
at the sound of my mistress's name,
but I find that hard to believe.
When she's at home...
Is this a good color on me?
...she just seems like any other girl.
She's sensitive, awkward, and
inclined toward loneliness.
Just your average everyday girl.
What do you think it's like to be in love?
I guess I'll never know...
At work, they started a rumor that
my favorite food is raw bear meat.
How could someone like me ever know love?
Then, one night...
My mistress came back in a daze.
sway
I was terribly worried about her.
But...
Ever since then, she's been
laughing and smiling so much.
It's as if she's under a magic spell!
Today they told me I was
the incarnation of an ogre!
Isn't that a silly thing to say?
A single match can start a fire!
Red Saves the Day!!
Which should I go with?
She does appear happy.
Well, you watch the house!
And she somehow seems prettier than before.
See you later!
What could have happened to her?
Just kidding.
I know exactly what it is.
Listen to me, you goon of a man...
If you ever do anything
to make my mistress sad,
I'll see that you pay.
Freezing Sentai Gelato 5!
Fudo is going to infiltrate
Gekko's fortress?!
We head to the amusement
park after Fudo-senpai...
But there, we see...
Pathetic humans!
I'll teach you the true meaning of fear!
Episode 3     At Last, the Amusement Park
smack
Love After World Domination, Episode 3:
"At Last, the Amusement Park"!